HANIF RIZKYANA



ABOUT

Hanif is an automation specialist with a strong background in data analysis and marketing. Known for his attention to detail and creative problem-solving, he excels in enhancing business operations through efficient solutions. please visit the portofolio to see what hanif can do.

PORTOFOLIO

BIT.LY/Hanif_Porto

CHATBOT

BIT.LY/HanifGPT

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer (Automation Specialist)

Independet 2023 - PResent

Developed and implemented various automation solutions to streamline business processes, enhancing efficiency and accuracy across multiple projects.

Branch Manager

JNE SARIMAS 2020 - 2023

Oversaw branch operations, managed a team, and implemented strategies to improve service delivery and customer satisfaction, significantly reducing outstanding issues.

Jr Marketing Analyst

2019 - 2020 МОКА

Carried out market research, evaluated sales data, and assisted in refining marketing campaigns to help shape data-informed marketing strategies.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS INDONESIA

Business Bachelors Degree / 2014-2018

TECHNICAL SKILL

PYTHON AI API **SELENIUM MYSQL**

> **GOOGLE API POWER POINT**

> > **AND MORE**

ADVANCE SKILL

DATA ANALYSIS PROMPT ENGINERING

AUTOMATION PRESENTATION

PRODUCT

AND MORE

SOFT SKILL

PROBLEM SOLVING PRODUCT DESIGN TECH SAVY

> Leadership **Team Work**

> > **AND MORE**



+62 85923671003



Hanifrizkyana@gmail.com